## **CLAYTON GOFF**

204B Olive Street,, Santa Cruz, CA 95060

Telephone: (831) 239-9766 Email: cltngoff@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/Clayto30 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/clayton-goff-8545b31b2

Excelled in Coding Bootcamp and ready to apply full-stack web development skills including front end, JavaScript, restful API, and TDD using Jest framework. Effective and valued team member who makes significant contributions to the organization's goals by focusing on solutions. Currently applying critical thinking and reasoning to the customer experience in a fast-paced tech startup environment. Have rapidly assimilated new skills while diligently focused on the implementation of new policies, training Support Team and working closely with the engineering team. Preceded by 11 years as a dedicated case-manager for adults with mental health diagnoses and/or disabilities in state-licensed homes and facilities. The role demanded strong people skills in managing difficult and challenging client cases, as well as staff and operations.

## **EDUCATION**

University of California, Berkeley Extension Coding Bootcamp Santa Cruz, CA Completed July 2021 University of California, Santa Cruz B.A. Philosophy Santa Cruz, CA Completed Fall 2019

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

AtoB, Tier 2 Support

San Francisco, CA Dec. 2021-2020-present.

Develop new processes and policies for escalated support issues in a fast-growing company Communicate with BPO team to enhance understanding and integrate new solutions Independently construct ongoing strategies to solve common and new challenges Collaborate with Engineering team using detailed information using Linear

Warrior Made, Customer Experience Support

Santa Cruz, CA Feb. 2020-Dec. 2021

Implement the core values and processes of the customer experience
Proficiency in written, electronic communications, with a focus on email and LiveChat
Grow to new platforms and media in order to provide a well-rounded support
Develop strong written communication and self-start to maximize organization and efficiency

Front St. Inc (various facilities), Mental Health Coordinator

Monterey, CA Nov. 2018 – Feb. 2019

Provide case management with a focus on skill development, wellness and recovery Lead staff in providing care for eight residents in a state-licensed housing facility, while coordinating staff trainings, schedules, and staff development

Responsible for a variety of tasks including linking clients to services to providing intensive clinical or rehabilitation, development of services based on Individual Program plans

## REFERENCES

Please Inquire for References' Contact Information as Needed

**Helen Moses-Happ**, Director of Customer Support, Warrior Made **Mason McGinley**, QA at AdCellerant, formerly Teaching Assistant at Coding Bootcamp **Elisa Silva**, Earned Media Manager at AdCellerant, formerly EIC at Warrior Made